many many thanks to our friends from the
media I've been asked to say a few words
just to wrap things up that I'm trying
to think of what I really can't say
because in between dancers from the
media and from the rest of them all but
there are a couple things I guess first
of all I mean I mean well done it you
know I've never run America but I have
done a bit running in my life and I know
how hard long-distance is I mean to do
it in as you said in another part of the
world with conditions that really are
beyond anything I think that any of us
have ever experienced which brings a
whole view element to the challenges of
doing extreme sports extreme endurance
sports it's not to be underestimated and
I have a smaller story to share with you
I mean you are absolutely fearless and I
think what you did in terms of taking on
this challenge dealing with all of the
things that geopolitics and Earth's
stuff like that throws at us shows the
resilience as well but I know this so
last week I was in Hong Kong and I
happen to
[Music]
and it was good that he was in the red
eye and you know I mean you just dug
deep and clearly you knew what he wanted
achieve not just to to be the winners
but to only person implements so I mean
it's absolutely tremendous and I'd like
everybody to I mean you made yourself
proud you may have led proud and you
certainly made the Philippines brown so
congratulations yes I'm gonna kill you
but I just wanted to say briefly is this
really who was to not differently to the
athletes because I know
sort of reasonable athletes and I know
how mentally it is important you think
you're going to do something and how
tough it is when that something actually
gets changed at the last minute it's
actually quite hard sports so I mean
real kudos to the athletes but I think
also to all of the colleagues in FWD and
America organizers who recognize that
obviously this is a tremendous amount of
commitment been put in by a whole lot of
people athletes and organizers to be
able to deal with a completely
unexpected left field event such as
geopolitical tensions getting in the way
of being a great secure and this is
where I said you know there are some
really critical things around this is
not like because the elements in the
Arctic are are very finite in terms of
what they think the implications living
etc I think it was incredible incredible
thing and for me you know I am proud of
what FWD and the organizers were able to
do because this is kind of a bit like in
the end of life and this really is what
FWD is about which is making sure that
mentally and also financially
when life throws you a curveball which
unfortunately does more often than we
will actually like you have the
wherewithal to be able to deal with it
it may not be what we wanted with a visa
if you can get a common to be able to
work around it and I think as I say this
is really what its really embraced at
home you know get ready to live
celebrate living and I'd be ready for
anything that my first new sort of
mentality so congratulation I mean
something eyes like 10 minutes or so for
the not here so magnificent performance
like everybody and again for like an end
up by saying do exist
I absolutely it or of your achievement
for hours 10 minutes is a pretty decent
time actually in any matter to be
perfect officers they learn running
around on ice and fighting in cold winds
and so on and so forth it was terrific
and if we do get a chance to do it all
over again expectations with you said
the power really wide but brilliant job
we are so proud of you would've
delighted you came home safely
successfully and proudly flying
like so well done I concur to do